准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
遇见复仇者
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
等着呢
Wait for it
准时百分比
100%
新的一天也会偏头痛
Another day, another migraine
偏
Mi
准时百分比
12%
头痛
graine
在蟹堡王上班是不是很棒啊  章鱼哥
Isn't it great working at the Krusty Krab, Squidward?
是不是
Isn't it?
在这上班
Working here?
确实很棒
Yeah, great
确实
Yeah
没错
Oh, yeah
对
Yes
你先等着  章鱼哥
Hold that thought, Squidward
我一大早还得去停船场志愿捡垃圾呢
I'm due in the parking lot
for early morning litter patrol
愿海神王闪耀在我的收获之上吧
May Neptune shine brightly on my harvest
垃圾烦死我
垃圾
Litter
看来有谁很想念垃圾篓子了
Looks like someone missed the trash basket
对吧  糖果包装纸先生
huh, Mr. Candy Wrapper?
现在的小孩子啊
Kids these days
这么猖獗的我还没见过
I've never seen such an epidemic
起码也不会再继续扔了
Well, at least it's all over now
这些垃圾都是哪来的
Where is all this litter coming from?
有我在  你休想
Not on my watch
先生我跟你说
Sir, I will have you know
乱扔垃圾是违法的
it's against the law to litter
你又能拿我怎么办  报警吗
What are you going to do, call the police?
没错
Yes
怎样了  小警察
How's it going, lieutenant?
就这么说吧  我希望那个乱扔垃圾的
Well, let's just say I hope our litterbug there
留了点肚子去吃甜点
saved room for his just desserts
没错
Yeah
甜点
Just desserts
[ desserts（甜点）
与 just deserts（罪有应得）谐音 ]
随你便
Whatever
海绵宝宝  你难道不知道他是谁吗
SpongeBob, don't you know who that is?
谁
Who?
他就是告密掐脖复仇者
That's the Tattletale Strangler
谁啊
Who?
告密掐脖复仇者
The Tattletale Strangler
通缉
告密掐脖复仇者
他发过誓要掐死送他坐牢的人
He's promised to strangle anyone who turns him in
他貌似有点气咱们  章鱼哥
He seems kind of angry with us, eh, Squidward?
章鱼哥
Squidward?
Squidward
坐苦牢去吧  复仇者
You're going to do time, Strangler
苦死你
Hard time
警官们好
Hi, officers
所以他是不是要去坐牢了
So he's going to jail, right?
谁  复仇者吗
Who, Strangler?
没错  复仇者
Yeah, Strangler
是啊
Oh, yeah
他得去坐好长时间的牢呢
He's going to jail for a long time
跟我一模一样
That looks like me
放心好了  海绵宝宝
Don't worry, SpongeBob
他可掐不到你
he won't be able to strangle you
没错  他被铐得可严实了
Yeah, we got him chained up real good
绝对逃不走的
He'll never get away
又来了
Not again
没错  他逃走了
Yup, he got away
你们两位好心警官会保护我吗
You nice officers will protect me, right?
我们可不是保镖  小子
We ain't bodyguards, kid
对  再看到他就打电话找我们
Yeah, give us a call if you see him again
告密人
tattletale
那些警官说得对
Those officers are right
我需要保镖
I need a bodyguard
蟹堡王
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
有疯子盯上我了
There's a maniac after me
我需要保镖
I need a bodyguard
我在海军得五次金钳奖不是没道理的
I wasn't five-time golden claws in the navy for nothing
等他看到我动手
When he see me moves
一定会落荒而逃
he'll be running scared
所以你说的小恶棍在哪
So where is this little bully
公园里吗
down at the park?
汽水店吗
The soda shop?
他长什么样  小子
What does he look like, eh, boy?
这就是他  蟹老板
This would be him, Mr. Krabs
通缉
告密掐脖复仇者
The Tattletale Strangler
海绵宝宝你走开
Go away, SpongeBob
带走你的死亡阴云
Take your death cloud with you
狂暴酒馆
求抱抱
Hold me
公交站
就这样了  我得离开裤头村
That's it, I got to get out of town
等找到保镖再回来
till I can find a bodyguard
保镖是吧
Bodyguard, huh?
我应该可以帮上你的忙
I might be able to help you out
你不明白  先生
You don't understand, mister
镇上最可怕的人要伤我  我需要保护
I need protection from the scariest guy in town
这是他照片
Here's his picture
通缉
他不是很能打的样子啊
He doesn't look so tough
我举报了他
I tattled on him
现在他想心狠手辣掐死我
and now he wants to strangle me
with his diabolical hands
希望他手不脏
I hope they're not dirty
这边目击者太多了
There's too many witnesses around here
小子我跟你说
Listen, kid
我可以当你保镖
I could be your bodyguard
这是我名片
Here's my card
保镖
告密掐脖复仇者
我觉得不错
Looks good to me
录用你了
You're hired
我已经觉得安全多了
I feel safer already
接着要干啥
What's next?
那疯子可能无处不在
Well, the maniac could be anywhere
穿着伪装
wearing a disguise
他可能是那个老头
He could be that old man
或者那个婴儿
Or that baby
或者那颗石块
Or that pebble
或者那根树枝
Or that stick
或者那张坑蒙拐骗胡子店的小票
Or that receipt
for the Phony Baloney Mustache Emporium
那是我的
That's mine
保镖啊  我现在受到你严密的保护了
Oh, bodyguard, my body is in your guarding hands
要先干啥呢
What do we do first?
建议去一个比较僻静的地方
I suggest we go to a nice quiet, secluded location
比如垃圾箱后边  或者黑暗的小巷子
like behind an old dumpster, or a dark alley
可以来我家把灯全都关了
We could go to my house and turn off all the lights
正好
Perfect
这样就不会有谁听到你被掐死
That way no one could hear you being strangled
我是说
I mean, uh
受保护
protected
完美
Perfect
没错  好棒
Yes, excellent
可我得先要办点事
But first I got to do a few errands
那行  不过要快点
Okay, but let's make it quick
我的天性就是快
"Quick" is my middle name
来看看  纸巾
Let's see, paper towels
这包写的是  附近最好的卫生纸
This one says, "Best paper towel around"
这包写的是  全镇最好的卫生纸
This one says, "Best paper towel in town"
全镇
"In town"
附近
"Around"
全镇
"In town"
附近
"Around"
你怎么看  保镖
What do you think, bodyguard?
能快点进你家门就行
Whatever gets us to your house quicker
那我全买了
I'll take both
干洗  请稍候
给你  海绵宝宝先生
Here you go, Mr. SquarePants
哪里有问题吗
Is there something wrong?
我不太确定这是不是我的裤子
I'm not sure if these are my pants
香水
这份怎么样  保镖
How about this one, bodyguard?
太难闻了吗
Too overbearing?
就不能直接到你家去吗
Can we just go to your house?
到了  海绵府
Here we are, SquarePants Manor
保镖  让我借着这个机会
Bodyguard, let me just take this opportunity
对你说  你这保镖强到人人都想要
to say you're the best bodyguard
a fellow could hope to have
少给我讲肉麻话
All right, enough of the sappy talk
把门打开  这样我才能掐死你
Open the door so I can strangle you
我是说
I mean, uh
呛死你
choke you
我是说
I mean, uh
掐坏你气管
crush your windpipe
我是说
I mean
保护我
Protect me?
谢了
Thanks
别客气  复仇者
Don't mention it, Strangler
我是说保镖
I mean "bodyguard"
我把钥匙放哪去了
Now, where did I put my key?
二十分钟后
找不到啊
Well, I can't find them
你要来看下吗
Do you want to take a look?
别管钥匙了
Forget the key
爬窗户得了
Let's climb through this window
我够不着
I can't reach it
能跳到我肩膀上面来吗  小子
Do you think you can you hop up on my shoulders, kid?
可以啊
Sure
穿上带刺的钉鞋  一切皆有可能
With these spiky cleats, anything is possible
钉鞋
"Cleats"?
把脚从我眼窝里拿开
Get your feet out of my eye sockets
我尽力了  可我鞋卡你眼角膜里了
I'm trying, but my cleats are stuck in your corneas
下去
Get off
六小时后
别生气了  保镖
Don't be mad, bodyguard
我去拿放地毯底下的钥匙
Let me just grab the key I keep under the mat
这样就能进去了
and we can get inside
找到你了  你个小坏蛋
There you are, you little rascal
现在把钥匙插进锁里
Now to put it in the lock
激活制动栓
which should activate the tumblers
然后就能开门了
thus opening the door
踏进去
Step inside
关上门
Close the door
好  我们到了
Well, here we are
我总算让你孤身一人了
I finally got you all alone
对啊  是不是很棒
I know, isn't it great?
你这下可要遭报应了  告密人
Now you're going to get yours, tattletale
惊喜
Surprise
恭喜海绵宝宝100%准时
庆祝我百分百准时上班的惊喜派对
A surprise party to celebrate
my perfect on-time percentage at work?
你们怎么知道的
How'd you guys know?
是你送我们的邀请函上写的
It's on the invitations you sent us
派对
来跳舞吧
Let's boogie
大家再见  谢谢参加
Bye, everybody, thanks for coming
再见蟹老板
Bye, Mr. Krabs
再见痞老板
bye, Plankton
再见珊迪
bye, Sandy
再见拉里
bye, Larry
再见珍珍
bye, Pearl
再见泡芙老师
bye, Mrs. Puff
再见章鱼哥
bye, Squidward
再见  剩下的
bye, the rest
总算孤身一人了
Alone at last
什么
What?
所以就剩咱俩了
So we're all alone now?
只有你跟我还有地板了
Just you, me and the floorboards
不错
Yeah
生日快乐  海绵宝宝
Happy birthday, SpongeBob
你们怎么知道今天我生日的
How did you guys know today is my birthday?
我们只是照着邀请函上写的做而已
We just do what the invitations say
再来跳舞吧
Let's boogie some more
谢谢到来
Thanks for coming
又孤身一人了
Alone again
真的吗
Is it true?
全都走了吗
Everybody's gone?
今天没别的派对了吗
No more parties today?
要的东西全买到了吗
You've got everything you need now?
一个人都不剩吗  彻底只剩咱俩吗
Nobody's left, we're completely alone?
没错
Oh, yeah
这样的话
In that case
派对很好玩吧
Great parties, huh?
对不起  小胖
Sorry, tubby
你得走了
you got to go
等等  可以相信派大星的
Wait, we can trust Patrick
他可是我最好的朋友
He's my best friend
我可不能冒这么大的险
Well, uh, I can't take any chances
说不定  他就是复仇者
For all we know, uh, he could be the Strangler
我是复仇者
I'm the Strangler?
我早该知道的
I should have known
我得去自首
I got to turn myself in
原来派大星是复仇者
So Patrick's the Strangler
知人知面不知心
Gee, you think you know a guy
他不是复仇者
He's not the Strangler
不是吗
He's not?
我才是
I am
你没剃须膏怎么做到的
How'd you do that without shaving cream?
这是假胡子  你个白痴
It's a fake, you idiot
我到派对商店买的
I bought it at the party store
有谁说了派对吗
Did someone say "party"?
我受不了了
I can't take it
保镖别走  我需要保护
Wait, bodyguard, I need protection
出租船
快开船
Step on it
有个疯子在追我
I'm being chased by a maniac
我不安全
I'm not safe
回来
Come back
裤头村机场
终于啊
Finally
远离那家伙了
Away from that guy
好办法啊  保镖
Good idea, bodyguard
他肯定发现不到咱在上面
He'll never find us up here
想得真周到  保镖
Good thinking, bodyguard
复仇者可能就在那座飞机上
The Strangler could have been on that plane
警察局
保镖
Bodyguard
听好  小子
Look, kid
我不是你保镖
I'm not your bodyguard
我就是复仇者
I'm the Strangler
看见没
See?
通缉
告密掐脖复仇者
复仇者
The Strangler
干得漂亮  海绵宝宝
Good work, SpongeBob
你把复仇者送进牢里去了
You put the Strangler behind bars
至少那个黄色白痴不会威胁到我了
At least I'm safe from that yellow idiot
老弟
Hey, Mack
你犯什么事进来的
What are you in for?
恶作剧
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
恶作剧宫殿
派大星  我们到了
Well, Patrick, here it is
恶作剧宫殿
the Palace of Pranks
全裤头村最厉害的新奇道具商店
the greatest novelty shop in Bikini Bottom
最棒的恶作剧家都会来这买东西
All the greatest pranksters shop here
我就在这买了恶作剧道具脆脆果仁罐
This is where I got my gag seanut brittle can
脆脆果仁
天啊  脆脆果仁
Oh, boy, seanut brittle
给我
Give me
派大星等等  忘了里面有机关吗
Patrick, wait, it's a booby trap, remember?
少来了  海绵宝宝
Nice try, SquarePants
你这回肯定耍不到我
but it's not going to work this time
我要吃到你那好吃的脆脆果仁
I'm going to have some of your delicious seanut brittle
脆脆果仁呢
Where's the seanut brittle?
每次你一说这话就更好笑了  派大星
That gets funnier every time you say it, Patrick
走了  我们快进去
Come on, let's go inside
脆脆果仁
Seanut brittle
便宜的塑料道具味最好闻了
Nothing compares to the smell
of cheap plastic novelty items
恶作剧  小道具
Pranks, gags
还有恶心玩具一眼望不到边
and gross-out toys as far as the eye can see
我说的是不是都很对啊  派大星
Isn't it everything I said it would be, Patrick?
脆脆果仁
Seanut brittle
真是  又来了
Darn it, not again
很高兴又见到你了  海绵宝宝
Good to see you, SpongeBob
我的头号顾客最近过得怎样
How's my number one customer doing?
还不错  法兰克
Great, Frank
这是我朋友派大星
This is my friend, Patrick
他也想当恶作剧家
He wants to become a prankster, too
很高兴认识你  派大星
Well, pleasure to meet you, Patrick
这是你的第一课  孩子
That's your first lesson, son
一切恶作剧的祖师爷
The granddaddy of all pranks
握手整蛊电击器
the joy buzzer
这我不懂
I don't get it
不用懂的
You don't have to get it
恶作剧就是给恶作剧家整着玩的
The prank is for the enjoyment of the prankster
派大星  这位法兰克可是个大师
You see, Patrick, Frank here is the master
我所有恶作剧知识都是跟他学的
I learned all I know about pranks from him
法兰克  看看你都有些什么货
Okay, Frank, let's see what you've got
这份是今天早上刚进的
Well, this came in just this morning
吃点口香糖
Have some gum
爆炸口香糖  只要九块九毛五
Exploding chewing gum, only $9.95
爆炸糖
我不懂
I don't get it
一块钱能买什么
What can we get for one dollar?
一块钱可以买到这张假道具钱
One dollar will get you this fake gag dollar
让你朋友以为你真的有一块钱
Fool your friends into thinking
you've got a real dollar
还有些什么
What else have you got?
放屁坐垫
A whoopee cushion?
不行
Nah
假呕吐物
Fake vomit
不好
No
真呕吐物
Real vomit
就没什么好货吗
Don't you have anything good?
我倒是特地留了一样恶作剧道具
Well, there is one prank that I've been saving
给顶级头号恶作剧家用
for a real top-of-the-line prankster
隐身喷雾
危险
Invisible spray
隐身喷雾
可我看得到这玩意
But I can see it
派大星  想想用这玩意能做啥恶作剧
Gee, Patrick, just think of the pranks
we could pull with this
选得好
Good choice
小心点使那玩意  孩子
Now, be careful with that stuff, boys
会弄脏衣服的
It stains clothes
谢了  法兰克
Thanks, Frank
隐身喷雾
到手了  派大星
Here it is, Patrick
终极恶作剧道具
the ultimate prank
隐身喷雾
Invisible spray
要用这玩意来干什么
What are we going to do with it?
有了
I know
去喷公园长椅  再坐上去
We'll go spray the park bench and then sit on it
路人会当我们在浮空
and when people walk by, we'll be floating in midair
他们居然浮空了
They're floating in midair
怎么做到的
How do they do that?
好终极的恶作剧
That's the ultimate prank
好点子  海绵宝宝
Good idea, SpongeBob
那就开始吧
Well, let's get started
我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready
你为什么要把裤子脱掉
Any particular reason you took your pants off?
这玩意会弄脏衣服  对不
Well, that stuff stains clothes, right?
说得确实  派大星
That it does, Patrick, that it does
想得真周到
Good thinking
给  你来拿一会
Here, hold this a second
派大星  罐子给我
Okay, Patrick, give me the can
既然喷公园长椅是我想出来的点子
I think since spraying the park bench was my idea
就应该让我来喷
I should get to spray it
派大星  喷公园长椅是我的点子
Patrick, spraying the park bench was my idea
对啊  可我之前说那是好点子
Yeah, but I said it was a good idea
快点给我
Give me that thing
隐身喷雾还真有用
The invisible spray works
大家看向右边
And on your right if you look
可以看到两个裸男在抢一罐颜料
you'll see two naked guys fighting over a can of paint
老天爷啊  派大星
Oh, my gosh, Patrick
快帮我找衣服
help me find our clothes
我得用手拿给你了  海绵宝宝
I got to hand it to you, SpongeBob
你样子真好笑
You look kind of funny
右手  你哪去了
Righty, where are you?
不许欺负右手
No one messes with Righty
看看你有什么感想
We'll see how you like it
是不是给你了空洞的感觉
Kind of gives you an empty feeling, huh?
是啊
Yeah
看得出来你什么意思
I see what you mean
没有肚量就没有成功
No guts, no glory
几句冷笑话后
这玩意应该是空了
I think this thing is empty
不可能吧
Oh, no, it can't be
这下还怎么搞终极恶作剧
How are we going to pull off the ultimate prank?
可谢谢你了  派大星
Thanks a lot, Patrick
隐身喷雾都被你用光了
You used the last of it
我好像找到裤子了
I think I found our pants
给  这条是你的
Here, these are yours
别管裤子了  派大星
Forget the pants, Patrick
回家把身上的喷雾都洗掉
Let's get home and wash this paint off
海绵宝宝  能问下现在几点了吗
Hey, SpongeBob, do you know what time it is?
好啊  现在
Sure, it's
看不见点半
half past invisible
时候也不早了
Gee, it's getting late
来问下这个人
Let's ask this guy
先生  能问下现在几点吗
Excuse me, sir, but do you have the time?
好的  现在两点五十
Sure, it's ten to 3:00
谢了
Thank you
不用谢
Don't mention it
不用啥玩意
Don't mention what?
是谁说的话
Who said that?
我
Me
鬼啊
Ghosts
我才不是鬼
I'm no ghost
那人跟他那个会开船的眼球真胆小
The nerve of that guy and his driving eyeballs
等一下  派大星
Wait a second, Patrick
我脑子生出了个好办法
my brain just hatched an idea
生来给我听
Lay it on me
我们隐身了  对吧
Okay, we're invisible, right?
对啊
Yeah
要是那人以为我们是鬼
If that guy thought we were ghosts
我们就能缠上裤头村的所有人了
we could haunt everybody in Bikini Bottom
好一个终极恶作剧
It's the ultimate prank
击个掌
High five
一起去吓几个笨蛋吧
Let's go scare us some suckers
奇怪  我明明听到有说话声的
That's funny, I thought I heard voices
我明明把这杯花生汁放桌子上的
I thought I left that glass of peanut juice on the table
我昨天不是把这个旧台灯扔了吗
And didn't I toss that old lamp out yesterday?
我什么时候淘到了这么多
And since when did I acquire all these
派大星的肖像画
portraits of Patrick?
我们是鬼
We're ghosts
果然是你们
I knew it was you guys
别开玩笑了
All right, joke's over
床单都拿掉
Take off the sheets
还真的是鬼
It is ghosts
德克萨斯
天啊  她被吓得不轻
Boy, we really scared her
谁会是我们的下一个受害者呢
Who's going to be our next victim?
更好的问法是  谁不是
A better question would be, "Who isn't?"
双层深海低脂黑蛋糕
Double-dark deep-sea light diet cake
你马上就是我的了
You will soon be mine
鬼啊
Ghosts
卡哇帮嘎
Cowabunga
鬼啊
Ghosts
[ toast（面包）与 ghost（鬼）谐音 ]
面包啊
Toast
鬼啊
Ghosts
裤头村时报
全城被吓
官方认证了
It's official
我们是史上最棒的恶作剧家
we're the greatest pranksters ever
全镇人都以为我们是鬼了
The whole town thinks we're ghosts
确实
Yeah
最后再吓一位
There's only one guy left to scare
裤头村所有人就都全被咱整过了
and we'll have pranked everybody in Bikini Bottom
唯有蟹老板暂未被鬼上身
他表示"我不怕鬼"
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
唯有蟹老板暂未被鬼上身
他表示"我不怕鬼"
上面写着他不怕鬼
It says he isn't scared of ghosts
等着瞧好了
We'll see about that
蟹堡王
关
鬼
Ghosts
我才不怕什么鬼
I ain't afraid of no ghosts
水手都知道驱鬼的办法
Every sailor knows a ghost won't come near a fella
就是戴着斑点领巾
as long as he's wearing his spotted neckerchief
还带着风干的海妖
and his dried-up sea leprechaun
狐媚
带点金子也算不了什么
And a bit of gold never hurt
不过为了以防万一
But to be on the safe side
我穿的裤子上还打了个结
I'm also wearing me pants in a melvin knot
脚上还戴了木制防抖支撑器
got me shivering timber brace
我脖子后边的毛也用胶带揭下来了
and the hairs on the back of me neck are taped down
我还披了件防鬼用的盔甲
And I'm all wrapped up in a suit of anti-ghost armor
要是全都失效了
And if none of this stuff works
还有秘密武器
I've got me secret weapon
鬼怪转移器
The specter deflector
你们这些鬼快来抓我啊
So just try and get me, you ghosts
放马过来
Bring it on
蟹老板
Krabs
什么
What?
蟹老板  我们要来缠上你了
Krabs, we've come to haunt you
退后  我全副武装
Stay back, I'm well-armed
我警告你们
I'm warning you
一定要逃出去
I got to get out of here
你逃不出去的  蟹老板
You can't escape, Krabs
我们把门粘起来了
We glued the door shut
胶水
你们抓不到我
You'll never get me
逃不掉的  蟹老板
Nice try, Krabs
我们把玻璃都换成橡胶了
but we replaced all the glass with rubber
太晚了  蟹老板
Too late, Krabs
我们已经把马桶堵上了
we've already clogged all the toilets
鬼魂  我求你们放我一马吧
Please, spirits, leave me be
整到他了  海绵宝宝
We got him good, SpongeBob
等等  派大星
Wait, Patrick
我又想到了个点子
I've got one more idea
你要付出代价  蟹老板
You're going to pay, Krabs
鬼魂不要  拜托
No, spirits, please
代价
Pay
不要
No
代价
Pay
不要
No
不要烧我的钱
Don't burn me dollar
哟哟哟  这不是海绵宝宝跟派大星吗
Well, well, well, if it isn't SpongeBob and Patrick
我不认识你说的是谁
I know not these names of which you speak
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
海绵宝宝  我们显形回来了
SpongeBob, we're visible again
原来你们两个就是裤头村的鬼啊
So you two are the Bikini Bottom ghosts
真的很对不起  蟹老板
We're really sorry, Mr. Krabs
求你别把我们剁成块吃了
Please don't chop us up into little pieces and eat them
没事  我是吃素的嬉皮士
come on, boys, I'm hip
我在你们这把年纪也搞恶作剧的
I pulled my share of pranks when I was your age
让我笑得可开心了
had me some laughs
我们今晚就是这样的  对吧
That's what we did tonight, right?
我们笑得可开心了
We had a good laugh
来吧  一起笑
Come on, laugh with me
你们为什么要光着身子
Any particular reason you boys are naked?
隐身喷雾会弄脏衣服
Yeah, the invisible paint stains clothes
那是当然了
Of course it does
快回家吧  免得有谁看到你们裸体
Well, you two better hurry home
before someone sees you nude
对啊  真那样我会被尬死的
Yeah, I think I'd die of embarrassment if that happened
我也一样
Me, too
这种事可不能有  对吧
No, wouldn't want that, would we?
都这么晚了
It's getting late now
你们两个恶作剧家该走了
You pranksters better get going
蟹老板  谢谢你对我们这么好
Mr. Krabs, thanks for being such a good sport
不用谢
Don't mention it
蟹老板啊  总是会为我着想
That Mr. Krabs, always looking out for me
真是个好人
What a guy
没错
Yeah
蟹堡王倾情奉献
The Krusty Krab presents
活生生的裸体恶作剧家
live nude pranksters
由裤头村的鬼领衔主演
Starring the Bikini Bottom ghosts
派大星
Patrick
怎么了
Yeah?
蟹堡王
早知道就买放屁坐垫了
We should have bought the whoopee cushion